

Nadja Edström

073 027 00 36 · nadja.e@outlook.com https://nadjae.github.io/portfolio/

About Me

An ambitious and positive UX design student with a passion for interface design that is both beautiful and inclusive. Currently learning more about web development during my spare time.

Language





Certificate

May 2018

ITIL Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management, AXELOS Global Best Practice.

Skills

Wireframing Prototyping User Research User testing

Illustrator Axure Adobe XD Figma

Java Python **HTML** CSS **JavaScript**

References

Available upon request.

Experience

January 2018 - June 2018

Server Operations Technician, Idenet

Part of the server monitoring team and team leader for the staff working night shifts. Incident manager during temporary server outages. Certified in IT service management (ITIL).

August 2016 - January 2018

IT Support Technician, Idenet

Solved varying IT related problems via incoming calls. Also handled account and email set up.

Education

2019 - 2022

Interaction Design, Stockholm University

Studying the entire design process from concept development to fully functioning prototypes, human-computer interaction, design and programming.

2020

Fashion Sketching & Illustration, University of Borås (15 ECTS).

2018-2019

Bachelor of Science, KTH Royal Institute of Technology Studied one year.

Volunteer work

2018 - 2019

Business committee, KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Part of the business committee of the chapter for Open Entrance at KTH.